In a time when many people around the globe are in lockdown and unable to attend the gym, emphasis has been placed on home exercising.
在全球许多人处于封锁状态、无法去健身房的时期，居家锻炼受到了重视。
Fears of a sedentary life and piling on the pounds are forcing many to find novel ways to move the body and stretch their muscles.
对久坐生活和体重增加的担忧，迫使许多人寻找新颖的方式来活动身体、拉伸肌肉。
You don’t need to pump iron or have expensive equipment like rowing and cycling machines to help you stay fit.
你不必举铁，也无需拥有划船机、健身单车这类昂贵器材，一样可以保持健康。
Exercising is not just important for your body, but also your mind.
锻炼不仅对身体有益，对心理也同样重要。
A study by Dr. Andrea Dunn at the Cooper Research Institute in Dallas, Texas found patients who did daily 35-minute walks per week experienced a 47% reduction in their depression levels.
得克萨斯州达拉斯库珀研究所的安德里亚·邓恩博士开展的一项研究发现，每周坚持每天散步35分钟的患者，抑郁程度降低了47%。
Cardiovascular exercise, often simply called cardio, is designed to keep your heart rate up, which in turn will strengthen your heart and improve your general fitness.
有氧运动通常简称为有氧训练，这类运动旨在提高心率，进而增强心脏功能、改善整体健康状况。
Many of us are turning to activities like skipping with an old rope, or watching one of the many ‘fitness experts’ who produce exercise videos online.
很多人开始选择一些简单的运动，比如用旧绳子跳绳，或是观看健身达人发布的线上锻炼视频。
Walking is another great aerobic activity to help you increase your blood circulation.
散步也是一项极佳的有氧运动，有助于促进血液循环。
There are many affordable pedometers which can be worn like a watch and used to track your steps, heart rate, sleeping patterns and even your blood oxygenation levels.
市面上有许多价格实惠的计步器，可像手表一样佩戴，用于记录步数、心率、睡眠模式甚至血氧饱和度。
You don’t even have to step outside, with many simply power walking or jogging round their gardens or up and down their hallways.
你甚至不用出门，很多人就在自家花园里快走或慢跑，或是在走廊里来回踱步。
Practising yoga or Tai Chi can help to keep our bodies supple, which in turn can lower joint pain and help to protect us from injury.
练习瑜伽或太极有助于保持身体柔韧性，进而减轻关节疼痛、预防受伤。
Finally, strength and resistance training can be done at home by simply lifting bags of rice or boxes instead of heavy weights in the gym.
最后，力量和抗阻训练在家也能进行，不用去健身房举重物，只需举起几袋大米或几个箱子就行。
There are many ways to help us stay mobile, and indeed these online exercise routines can be carried over in our lives long after lockdown is lifted.
保持身体灵活的方法有很多，而且这些线上锻炼方式，在封锁解除后的很长一段时间里都能继续存在于我们的生活中。
For those of us who moan about our busy lives stopping us from hitting the gym, ten minutes a day with a rope or a bag of rice may not only help our fitness, but our mental health too.
对于那些抱怨工作太忙没时间去健身房的人来说，每天花十分钟跳绳或举米袋，不仅能增强体质，还能改善心理健康。